scribie.com 2019-03-03

# Scribie Audio/Video Transcription | Privacy Policy

##  Audio/Video Transcription Service 

We collect personal information in a number of ways when you visit our site or use our service. For example, you provide us with personal information when you register for an account or contact us by email. CGBiz Corporation automatically receives and records information from your browser, including your IP address and cookies. The personal information collected is used for billing, identification, authentication, service improvement, research, and contact.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from our servers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to access information when you sign in, store your preferences, and to keep you logged in. You can configure your browser to accept or reject these cookies.

### Information Sharing

CGBiz Corporation does not sell, rent or share personal information with any third parties under any circumstances. We may, however, disclose personal information when we believe it violates our Terms of Service or is appropriate to comply with the law, to protect our or our users' rights, as well as to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, and unlawful use of our site. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

### Client Data And Storage

CGBiz Corporation ensures that all the files, transcripts and data remain private and confidential. Access is restricted strictly on a need to know basis to our employees and contractors. All employees and contractors are required to sign a Non Disclousure Agreement before being allowed access to the data. Due to the sensitive nature of the recordings and transcripts we take privacy very seriously and make it our primary concern for all our customers.

### Information Security

We restrict access of information to CGBiz Corporation employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our transcription service. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

### Changes

CGBiz Corporation will notify customers by email about any significant changes in this policy.

### Privacy Questions and Feedback

If you have questions or concerns about CGBiz Corporation's Privacy Policy please contact us at [privacy@scribie.com](mailto:privacy@scribie.com). 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
